Aleksandar Veljković



LINKS

<u>linkedin.com/in/aleksandar-veljković</u> <u>4leksandarveljkovic.dev</u> github.com/zitj



EDUCATION

GYMNASIUM 2008 - 2012 Languages and social sciences

ITAcademy 2018 - 2019 Web design



EXPERIENCE

Angular Autmn Internship 2020 - 2021 Prime Holding, Niš, Serbia (hq: Plovdiv, Bulgaria)

Software Developer 2021 - PRESENT Kirey D.o.o, Niš, Serbia (hq: Milano, Italy)



SKILLS

Angular, TypeScript, JavaScript
Node.js, EXPRESS.js, SQL
Git, GitHub, SourceTree, JIRA
HTML5, CSS3, SCSS
Photoshop, Illustrator, Figma
SCRUM and AGILE methodologies
English (C2), Italian (C1)





PROFILE

Hello world, my name is Aleksandar Veljković I am 31 years old, born and raised in Leskovac, Serbia.

During my lifetime I had a chance to work variety of different jobs which makes me quite versatile and adaptive person. Always eager to learn and take on a new challenges.



+ 381 60 7 350 820

4leksandarveljkovic@gmail.com

